Guide to the David M. Kennedy Papers SC1115
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
David M. Kennedy papers
1914-2010
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Kennedy, David M.
SC1115
60.5 Linear Feet (42 boxes)
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Arrangement note
Files are arranged into five series: Personal, Professional & Administrative; Research Files; Teaching; Travel; and Computer Files.
Biographical/Historical note
David M. Kennedy is a Pulitzer Prize-winning historian specializing in American history. Born in Seattle, Kennedy received his A.B. in History from Stanford (1963) and MA (1964) and PhD (1968) from Yale. At Stanford since 1967, Kennedy is the Donald J. McLachlan Professor of History and the Director of the Bill Lane Center for the American West.
Professor Kennedy teaches both undergraduate and graduate courses in the history of the twentieth-century United States, American political and social thought, American foreign policy, American literature, and the comparative development of democracy in Europe and America. Reflecting his interdisciplinary training in American Studies, which combined the fields of history, literature, and economics, Professor Kennedy's scholarship is notable for its integration of economic and cultural analysis with social and political history. His 1970 Bancroft Prize-winning book, Birth Control in America: The Career of Margaret Sanger, embraced the medical, legal, political, and religious dimensions of the subject and helped to pioneer the emerging field of women's history. Over Here: The First World War and American Society (1980), a finalist for the Pulitzer Prize, used the history of American involvement in World War I to analyze the American political system, economy, and culture in the early twentieth century. Freedom From Fear: The American People in Depression and War (1999), which won the 2000 Pulitizer Prize, recounts the history of the United States in the two great crises of the Great Depression and World War II. Professor Kennedy is responsible for the recent editions of the popular history textbook The American Pageant. He is also the current editor of the Oxford History of United States series and Fellow of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of the professional files of Historian and Stanford Donald J. McLachlan Professor of History, Emeritus David M. Kennedy.
The Personal, Professional & Administrative series contains files related to Kennedy's activity within the Stanford University History Department, personal and professional correspondence, and his involvement in professional organizations and activities.
The Research Files series contain notes for publications, as well as drafts of articles and books. Most frequently represented topics include World War I and World War II, as well as general US and European history in the 20th century. Drafts of works in this series include: Freedom From Fear: The American People in Depression and War, 1929-1945; The American Pageant: A History of the Republic; Birth Control in America: The Career of Margaret Sanger; and Over Here: The First World War and American Society.
The Teaching series consists of various course lecture notes, readers, syllabi, and evaluations prepared for undergraduate and graduate courses taught by Kennedy.
The Travel series includes Kennedy's files related to conferences and other professional travel.
The Computer Files series includes various floppy diskettes created or maintained by Kennedy. This series is still in process.
World War, 1939-1945 -- Japanese Americans.; United States -- History; Depressions -- 1929.; Contraception -- History.; World War, 1914-1918.; World War, 1939-1945; Kennedy, David M.; Sanger, Margaret Higgins.
- Personal, Professional & Administrative, Series 1
  - School of Humanities and Sciences (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Humanities and Sciences Council, April 26 & 27, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - History (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Misc (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1984-85 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Humanities/Environ. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - NIE (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Jon Christensen (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Rallying Americans for War: 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Freedom from Fear (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Planning and Policy Board: Athletics; Tenured Faculty (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - PPB (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Planning & Policy Board Notes, Minutes, Information (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Any Questions? A HAndbook for Teaching Assistants (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Association Travel/Study Program (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Seine River College (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Book II Travel Concepts (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Anglo-American Law and the Logic of Experience (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Misc Speeches, Articles, Pubs (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - What "Building Block"? What "Model"? "Tides of Public Opinion" and Successive Party Systems in Cultural Perspective (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Agreement Under Article II, Section 2 of Atomic Energy Comission - Westinghouse Industrial Atomic Power Study Agreement, February 23, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Hoover Institution (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Raffaella Baritono (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - War and Region: the South and World War II by Morton Sosna (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - War and Region: the South and World War II by Morton Sosna (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Memorandum for the Secretary of State (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Articles (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Rob Schorman on David Potter (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - War, Revolution, and Peace (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - A Review of the Operational Relationship between Stanford University and Stanford University Bookstore (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Bookstore Management Proposal (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Jorge Velazquez (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Misc Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - NCC's (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Dept. Mtgs, '92-'93 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Salaries, '92-3 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Reappointments & Promotions '92-'93, 93-4 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Salaries, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Dept. Mtgs, 1993-94 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Policy Committee (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Graduate Program (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - History Dept. (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - History Commencement (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Humanities Center (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Department Meeting (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - International Initiative (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Abrahamson, James (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Doug Ayer (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Nathan Brostrom (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Bullock, George (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Camarillo (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Jim Campbell (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Cannon, Charles (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Castaneda, Antonia (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Gordon Chang (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Paul Chapman (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Cinel, Dino (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Cobble, Sue (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - David Coe (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Cummings, Bob (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Dahlin, Michel (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - David Danbom (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Bob Eager (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Geo. Forgie (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Frank Fox (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Louis Freedman (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Diane Ghirardo (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Konrad Hamilton (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Debbie Herman (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Debbie Herman Diss. (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - David Howard (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Jeffrey Thesis (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Richard Klingler (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Langston, Amanda (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Bill Leahy (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - John McGreevy (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Meyerowitz, Joanne (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Richard A. Nagareda (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Humanities Honors: Leanna Giannini and Nancy Page (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Mel Piehl (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Alison Post (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Dale Prentiss (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Reuben, Julie (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Rosalind Rosenberg (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Libby Rosenthal (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Rotter, Andy (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Linda Schott (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Schulman (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Dissertation Prospectus - Mark R. Schwehn 11/1/71 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Mark Paul (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Hum. Honors: Prud. Shepherd (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Richard Silver (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Christopher Sliney (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Richard Silver (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Dan Smith (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Spoehr, Luther (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Hum. Honors: Laura Treadgold (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Jorge Velazquez (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - John Manley DMK's SP6 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Janet Craycroft (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Leon Dayan (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - David Frank (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - GH (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - IJK & L (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - MN (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Lisa Marie Krause (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Paul Kurtis Preising (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Robb Westbrook (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Amy Worth (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Ann Wagenhals (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Alexander, Katy (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Atherton, Michael (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - John Chambers (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Butts, George (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Chase (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Cohen, Liz (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Lisa Cobbs (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - John Cooper (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Danbom, David (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Danver, Steven (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Dickinson, Frederick (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Duigan, Peter (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Mitchell, Fergus (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Niall Ferguson (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Jay Harris (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Michael P. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Jones, Trent (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Jordan, Donald E. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Kaufmann, William (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Klein, Melvyn (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Kloppenberg (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Kushner, Tony (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Lane, Bill (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Lightner, James (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Lowenthal, Kristi (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - McHugh (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - McGreevy, John (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Luigi Morelli (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Mosler, David (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Ogletree, Charles (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Ohren, D.L. (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Oldenburg, Kevin (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Peachin, Marilyn (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Perevezentsev (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Rick Perlstein (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Alison Post (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Richard Rahe (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Roth, Randolph (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Roberts, Donald (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Sandige, Hannelore (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Karin Sawislak (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur M. (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Linda Schott (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Paul Schroeder (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Scott (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Smith, William (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Ted Stevens (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Stolley, Dick (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Bill Tobin (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Turner, James (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Wasz, Bill (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Weingast (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Willrich, Mason (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Michael Willrich (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Moreno, Suzanne (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Zuckerman, Harriet (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Lilley, William (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - S, T, U, V, W... (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Italian Emigration Seminar (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - OAH Meeting, Philadelphia 1982 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Sabine MacCormack (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Letters of Recommendation (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Amer. Studies Seminar, 81-82 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - P-Q (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - R (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - S (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - T (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - U (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - V (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - W (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - X-Y-Z (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - A (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - B (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - C (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - D (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - E (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - F (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - G (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - H (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - I (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - J (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - K (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - L (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - M (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - N (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - O (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - P (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Q (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - R (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - S (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - T (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - U (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - X (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - V (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - W (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Y (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Z (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Rakove, Jack (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Nobles, Gregory (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Bloch, Ruth (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Italy, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Course Materials (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Oxford U. Press (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Commitments, 1994-95 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - AHA Program Committee 1985-86 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Atlantic Council (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - OAH - 1980 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence - Alumni Association (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - A & B (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - C (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - D-E-F (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - P & R (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - A (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - B (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - C (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - D (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - E (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - F (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - G (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - H (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - I (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - J (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - K (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - L (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - M (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - N (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - O (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Coulombe (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - PJF's, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Book Draft - Loose sheets/mater copy (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Bookstore - Follet Management Plan for Stanford University (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Bookstore - Follet Management Plan for Stanford University (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Bookstore - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Bookstore - Barnes and Noble Proposal (1 of 4), 1999 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Bookstore - Barnes and Noble Proposal (2 of 4), 1999 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Bookstore - Barnes and Noble Proposal (3 of 4), 1999 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Bookstore - Barnes and Noble Proposal (4 of 4), 1999 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Bookstore - Barnes and Noble Exhibits, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Bookstore - Closing Docs (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Bookstore - Closing Docs (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Bookstore - Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - University Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - University Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - University Correspondence, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - University Correspondence, circa 1995 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - University Correspondence, circa 1995 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Provost's Task Force, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - A Chronology of Stanford University and its Founders (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Democratic Caucus (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Gilder Lehrman Institute, 2001: The United States in Depression and War (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Preacher of Righteousness: The Social and Political Thought of Theodore Roosevelt. History Dept. Honors Thesis, Joshua D. Hawley, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Documents Project: Gilder Lehrman Institute of American History. The Great Depression, World War II, and the American West. June 24-30, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - The Other Stanford (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - West Coast Leadership Dialogue (binder) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Personal (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Soph. College (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Stanford '64 Reunion (Bernie Butcher) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - WGBH (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Correspondence - Unsorted (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Misc Papers - Articles, Reprints, Programs, Etc. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Studies in Church History, Vol. 29. Christianity and Judaism. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Donald McLachlan Chair in the School of Humanities and Sciences (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Report of the commission on Graduate Education (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - National Survey, David Demarest, Stanford University (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - FDR and the World Crisis, 1933-1945: Roosevelt and Hyde Park, 2007 Jul (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Faculty publications - departmental quality concerns (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Article: The World Wars (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - The E-College in the E-Age, Jack Rakove (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - The First Information Age (Draft), Richard White (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Redemption - draft (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Normandy (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Challenges of Humanities - Phoenix (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Research Retreat, 1992 Mar (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Richard White (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Publishing/Copyright Fees (Business) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - ACLS Review Board (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - American Leadership Forum (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - American Philosophical Society (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - American West (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Corresp. CARDS (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - AHA Program (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - CABSS (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Chicago Humanities Festival (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Center for Law in the Public Interest (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Columbia (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Commonwealth Club (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Commitments, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Corning, Peter (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Corresp. w/ clips/articles (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - General (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - Letters (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Personal, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Misc. Corresp. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Corresp. (Misc Sent) (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Personal Corresp. (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Corresp. (Requests) (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - Thank Yous (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - CHF (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Clinton/Cleveland - NY Times (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - C-SPAN (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - CUNY (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Cui Bono Article (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - D-Day Museum (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Department Emails 11/00 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Dept. of Defense (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Dutchess Community College (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - English Historical Review (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - "Freedom from Fear" (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Gilder-Lehrman (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Gingrich Article (LA Times) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Harmsworth Prof. Comm. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - "History Education" (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Huntington Lib. President (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Knight Fellows (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Knight-Ridder (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Invitations (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - LA Times Article (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Lukas Prize (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - MacArthur Foundation (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - McGovern, George (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Miller Center (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Congressional Quarry (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Nat'l Council for History Education (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - New-York Journal of America History (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Nie, Norman (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Oral Reports (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Oregon Cultural Heritage Commission (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Physics Comm. (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Random House (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - SIQSS (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - SMU (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - SSHI (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Society of American Historians (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Speeches, Commitments, etc. 1993-94 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Stanford Overseas Studies (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Stanford University Libraries (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Sunset (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - US Department of Education (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - "We Wear the Mask" Oxford Press (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - World Pension Forum (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - WGBH (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Archaeology of Silicon Valley (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Area One (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Physics/Applied Physics Rpts (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Teaching World War II - Organization of American Historians Annual Conference, St. Louis, Mo., 2000 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - National Standards for US History "A Vexed and Troubled People" (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Political (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Nanking Review (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Population/Census/Immig. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Dissertations/Papers (I) (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Dissertations/Papers (II) (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Bernard Bailyn (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Bill Bradley (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Finance Reform Op-Ed, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Stange vs. Regents of University of California (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - U.C. Davis Case (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - D.L.G. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Ethics in Society (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - FDR Library (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - FDR (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Meyer Festschrift (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Geral Sosbee Material (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Future of American Society (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Hubert Mee Interview (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - 8/e Illustrations (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Karel Kaplan (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - KCET-Wilson (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Khan (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Legal - Scotus Case (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Lewis and Clark (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Life: Our Century in Pictures (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - A Manifesto for the Fast World (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Mellon (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Man in Baghdad (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Kennedy - CV (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Papers by Kennedy (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Papers by Kennedy (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Sophomore College (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Ronald Reagan (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Ronald Reagan Article (Documents and Background) (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Ronald Reagan Article - Issues (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Eisenhower Essay (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Blum Project (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Bibliographies (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Gilder Lehrman Institute - The Great Depression: World War II and the American West (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Gilder Lehrman Institute - The Great Depression: World War II and the American West, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - America in the 21st Century: Beyond Misunderstandings, 2004 Jun 10-11 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Pulitzer Jury (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - OUP Delegates, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - WWII Film PBS (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Humanities Festival, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - AllLearn Forum/Aurora Forum (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Center for the West (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Committee on the U.S. Naturalization Test Redesign, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Influential Americans (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Depression Era Letters (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Census Papers (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Travel Study (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Oregon Episcopal School (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Woodrow Wilson Project (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Stanford (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Historian (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Undergraduate Program (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Stanford Graduate Colloquium, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - University Fellows (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - "CELL" (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - National Centennial Celebrations (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Liberty Memorial Museum (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Caribbean (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - L.A., 2006 Jan (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Ranking the Movie Presidents (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Regional Humanities Centers (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Reviews (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Judd, Tony - "Road to Nowhere, The" (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Reagan: Atlantic (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Sanger Film (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Sheehan, James: German Renaissance in America (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Sheehan, James (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Space Shuttle (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - State of the Union, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Suri, Jeremy (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Thomas, Keith (Box 37, Folder 12)